hey spring fans in today's installment
嘿，今天的春季粉丝
of spring tips we're gonna go look at
春天的技巧，我们要去看看
how to build complex integration flows
如何建立复杂的整合流程
and stream processing solutions using
和流处理解决方案，使用
spring cloud dataflow in previous videos
先前视频中的Spring Cloud Dataflow
we looked at spring integration as way
我们以 Spring Integration 的方式
of building messaging based and event
基于消息传递和事件的构建
based systems by integrating systems in
基于系统的集成
terms of events and then we we looked at
活动条款，然后我们看了看
how data flows from one node to another
数据如何从一个节点流到另一个节点
in terms of channels we then in a
就渠道而言，
subsequent video looked at how to build
随后的视频介绍了如何构建
messaging based micro-services using
基于消息传递的微服务使用
spring cloud stream spring cloud stream
spring-cloud-streamspring-cloud-stream
builds on spring integration and it
建立在 Spring Integration 的基础上
alleviates the need to specify the
减轻了指定
tedious sort of adapters the inbound and
繁琐的适配器入站和
outbound channels that we use in spring
我们在春季使用的出站渠道
Gration are still there but we don't
磨碎仍然存在，但我们没有
have to worry about how these things
不得不担心这些事情
talk to other nodes to other services
与其他节点交谈以使用其他服务
that that connectivity is is commoditize
连通性是商品
it's a it's extricated into a matter
这是一个沉迷于一件事情
into a configuration file and the rest
进入配置文件，其余的
of it is sort of apply and based on
这是一种适用并基于
convention so we get the result of
约定，所以我们得到的结果
systems that talk to each other but
互相交谈的系统
we've sort of a commoditize the
我们有点商品化了
transport and we do that using what's
运输，我们用什么做
called a spring cloud stream binder
称为 Spring Cloud Stream 粘合剂
there are several binders out there
那里有几种粘合剂
notably a
尤其是
rabbitmq and apache kafka so you can
rabbitmq和apache kafka，所以你可以
build spring cloud stream based services
建立基于Spring Cloud Stream的服务
micro services that talk to each other
互相交谈的微服务
using spring cloud stream rabbitmq or
使用 Spring Cloud Stream Rabbitmq或
spring cloud stream apache Kafka and we
Spring Cloud Stream Apache Kafka和我们
can just write code in terms of generic
可以只写通用的代码
spring integration channels none the
Spring Integration 渠道无
wiser are none the more aware of of
更加明智的是
these underlying components today we're
今天，这些基础组件
gonna get something called spring cloud
会得到所谓的春天云
dataflow spring cloud dataflow is a way
数据流弹簧云数据流是一种方法
of choreographing micro services based
编排微服务的基础
on spring cloud stream modules based on
在基于
spring cloud stream these modules accept
这些模块接受的 Spring Cloud Stream
data produced data and sometimes
数据产生的数据，有时
optionally both accept and produce data
可以选择接受和产生数据
and spring cloud dataflow rewrite or it
和Spring Cloud Dataflow重写或
sort of provides the configuration for
提供某种配置
the incoming in incoming channel and for
传入的传入通道和
the outbound channel so really the only
出站通道，所以真的是唯一
requirement to use your spring Cloud
使用Spring Cloud的要求
stream module in spring cloud dataflow
Spring Cloud Dataflow中的流模块
is that it produced some messages if
是它产生了一些消息，如果
it's gonna produce messages on a
它会在
well-known message channel called output
众所周知的消息通道称为输出
and then it accept messages if it's
然后它接受消息，如果
going to accept
要接受
on a well-known channel called input
在一个称为输入的知名频道上
spring cloud dataflow then just you know
春天的云数据流，那么你就知道
it stores the state for those
它为那些存储状态
descriptions it'll it knows about the
它会知道的描述
location of different spring cloud
Spring Cloud的位置
Stream modules either in terms of a
流模块在以下方面
maven repository or the docker image or
Maven存储库或Docker映像或
something like this and then you provide
这样的事情，然后您提供
a DSL you provide a description of this
您提供有关DSL的描述
of the composition a composition of
组成的
these different components in terms of
这些不同的方面
what's called a stream so again a stream
什么叫流，又叫流
is an infinite you know infinite
是无限的，你知道无限的
unending sort of thing that that handles
永无休止的东西
data and if in a potentially perpetual
数据以及是否可能永久存在
way a task is something different right
任务是不同的方式
a task is something that handles a
一项任务可以处理
finite amount of data a batch job for
批处理作业的有限数据量
example is a finite amount of data
例子是有限的数据
spring code data flow can manage and
Spring代码数据流可以管理和
sort of choreograph both tasks and
既有任务又有编舞
streams your task might for example be a
流您的任务可能例如是
spring batch job that you want you want
您想要的Spring Batch处理工作
managed and sort of administrable from a
可以从
single place so the spring cloud
单身的地方，所以春天的云
dataflow service does this for you it's
数据流服务为您做到这一点
a service that keeps it state in the
使它保持状态的服务
database you can then as an operator go
数据库，然后您可以作为操作员进入
to that that that server and then then
到那个服务器，然后
use it to mini plate or sort of monitor
用它来制作迷你平板或某种显示器
these um these streams and tasks so
这些嗯这些流和任务，所以
let's go do that I've got an FTP server
让我们去做，我有一个FTP服务器
running and and you may recall in the
运行，您可能会记得
spring negation video we we built a
春季否定视频，我们建立了一个
simple solution that took data from an
从
FTP directory and then we wrote it out
FTP目录，然后我们将其写出
to an FTP server and you know you know
到FTP服务器，您就知道了
lots of very very simple sort of
很多非常非常简单的
transformations and today we'll do the
转型，今天我们将做
same thing with even less code with even
同样的东西，甚至更少的代码
less sort of cognitive overhead we'll do
我们将减少的认知开销
that using data flow now data flow as I
现在使用数据流像我一样
say is agnostic about the underlying
说与底层无关
distribution mechanism remember it's
分布机制还记得
going to orchestrate or choreograph
去编排或编舞
rather your your different services on a
而是您在一个网站上的不同服务
distributed topology something like COD
分布式拓扑，例如COD
family or missiles or or yarn or
家庭或导弹或纱线
whatever right so we're gonna go ahead
没关系，所以我们要继续
and say data flow service and I'll bring
说数据流服务，我会带
in the the local data flow server here
在本地数据流服务器中
and that's it now of course we could
现在就可以了
provide a h2 data source if we wanted to
如果我们想提供h2数据源
or some other data source but it's
或其他一些数据源，但是
already gotten an in-memory embedded and
已经在内存中嵌入了
dated
过时的
to data source so it'll work just fine
到数据源，这样就可以正常工作
let's go ahead and hit hit generate
让我们继续前进，点击产生
open this up and our IDE it doesn't
打开它，我们的IDE不会
really matter which IDE and now we we do
真正重要的是哪个IDE，现在我们要做
as we always do with a sort of spring
一如既往的春天
boot based service these days we add an
这些天基于引导的服务我们添加了一个
annotation and the auto configuration
注释和自动配置
does the rest so we can spin it up on
剩下的了，所以我们可以旋转它
port 93 93 good quality ask you at work
港口93 93好的品质在工作中问你
I think you'll notice that first and
我想您会首先注意到
foremost when the application starts up
最重要的是当应用程序启动时
and then of course the application
然后是应用程序
itself is up and running and it is a
本身已经启动并正在运行，这是一个
fairly sophisticated API but it's
相当复杂的API，但是
already written for us so it's an API we
已经为我们编写了，所以这是一个API
don't have to worry about so we go here
不用担心，所以我们去这里
now to localhost 93 93 and you can see
现在到本地主机93 93，您可以看到
this is this the hypermedia or how tos
这是超媒体或如何
rest endpoints these are the endpoints
其余端点是端点
for the API itself you don't have to use
对于API本身，您不必使用
this API directly for the furthest thing
这个API直接用于最远的事情
from it right we can use the dashboard
从它开始，我们可以使用仪表板
so here I go to the dashboard and you
所以在这里我去仪表板，你
can see I've got several options here I
可以看到我在这里有几种选择
can get information about the server
可以获取有关服务器的信息
itself I can look at the analytics for
本身，我可以看看分析
for you know counters and things like
因为你知道柜台和类似的东西
this we'll come back to that in a bit
这一点我们会回到
I can look at the ongoing sort of jobs
我可以看看正在进行的工作
that are running or anything this is a
正在运行或任何这是一个
drill down of spring batch jobs in
深入挖掘Spring Batch作业
particular I can look at this the tasks
特别是我可以看一下这个任务
this is the overarching concept called a
这是一个称为
task and that might include spring batch
任务，其中可能包括Spring Batch处理
jobs for example and then I can I can of
例如工作，然后我可以
course look at the streams which we're
当然看看我们
going to create in a minute and the
将在一分钟内创建，
runtime now the runtime refers to the
运行时，现在运行时是指
components that are available the spring
弹簧可用的组件
Cloud stream apps and tasks that are
云流应用程序和任务
available for use right that are that
可用的使用权是
are running somewhere in this case on
在这种情况下正在某处运行
our local machine and the apps refers to
我们的本地计算机和应用程序指的是
the the modules the jars in this case or
在这种情况下，罐子的模块或
the the docker images or or whatever
码头工人图像或其他
that are available for use for
可用于
composition into complex solutions I can
我可以组成复杂的解决方案
register a new application by providing
通过提供注册新的应用程序
a name the type of component and a URL
名称组件的类型和URL
in this case maybe I'm
在这种情况下，也许我是
even URL something like maven io spring
甚至URL，例如maven io spring
you know it's such a cetera and that
你知道这是一个老样子
that would be that would even resolve on
那将甚至解决
your local your local maven repository
您本地的本地Maven存储库
or you could specify a repository that
或者您可以指定一个存储库
you want to use instead but what I what
你想用而不是我用什么
I want to do is I want to bulk import
我想做的是我要批量导入
some of the existing LEGO bricks that
一些现有的乐高积木
are provided by spring cloud dataflow
由spring cloud dataflow提供
and I can do that by going to the bulk
我可以通过大量操作来做到这一点
import applications and I can see here
导入应用程序，我可以在这里看到
there's four sets of pre-configured
有四组预配置
stream applications and two sets of
流应用程序和两组
pre-configured tasks applications the
预配置任务应用程序
streams are divided both in terms of the
流根据
type of binder RabbitMQ or Apache Kafka
活页夹RabbitMQ或Apache Kafka的类型
and the format whether it's a docker
以及格式是否为码头工人
image or a jar write it it knows how to
图片或罐子将其写入，它知道如何
deploy and execute both so we're gonna
既部署又执行，我们将
go ahead and import all of the RabbitMQ
继续并导入所有RabbitMQ
based maven coordinates for all the
基于所有的Maven坐标
existing jars so again this refers to
现有的罐子，所以这又是指
just a litany of different jars that
只是一连串的不同罐子
contain spring cloud stream applications
包含Spring Cloud Stream应用程序
or spring good applications really and
或真正的好应用程序和
when it's printed dataflow uses those
当它打印的数据流使用那些
those stream modules it's just gonna
这些流模块只是
start them up right that's what I mean
正确启动它们就是我的意思
it's gonna deploy them so now if we go
它会部署它们，所以现在如果我们去
to apps we can see all the different
对于应用程序，我们可以看到所有不同的地方
components and in the output here we can
组件，在输出中，我们可以
see specifically that there are three
具体看有三个
main kind of components reflected here
这里反映的主要成分
there are files are rather sources which
有文件是相当来源
produce a message on a well-known
产生一个知名的消息
channel called output there are
通道称为输出
processors which take a message in and a
接收消息的处理器和
well-known input channel and then write
知名输入通道再写
a message out on a well-known output
在知名输出上显示一条消息
channel and there are sinks which take
通道，有接收器
that in on a well-known input channel
在一个著名的输入通道上
right so these are spring clad stream
对，所以这些是春天穿的衣服
modules one and all the only convention
模块唯一的约定
required for them to be quality to be
他们必须具备的素质
usable as a source for a process there
可用作那里的过程的来源
is a sink is that they expose a spring
是一个水槽，因为它们暴露了春天
cloud stream channel called output and
云流通道称为输出和
input or sometimes both in the case of
输入或有时两者都输入
the the processors so now we've got
处理器，所以现在我们有了
these apps let's go ahead and build a
这些应用程序让我们继续构建一个
stream out of it so I'm gonna go to the
流出来，所以我要去
streams tab and here we can see that we
流标签，在这里我们可以看到我们
have no existing stream definitions
没有现有的流定义
let's go ahead and create one we're
让我们继续前进，创造一个我们
going to use this visual editor which
将使用此可视化编辑器
supports input as in one of two
支持两种输入之一
different ways we can do it using the
我们可以使用
spring cloud dataflow DSL or we can use
春天的云数据流DSL或我们可以使用
a visual way to do it so let's start
一种直观的方式来做，让我们开始吧
with the the DSL the DSL matches or
与DSL匹配的DSL或
looks pretty familiar to anybody who's
看起来对任何人都很熟悉
ever used bash so I'm gonna say that one
曾经用过bash，所以我要说
take data from the file source and write
从文件源获取数据并写入
it to the FTP sink the FTP sink needs
它到FTP接收器FTP接收器需要
some information about where to put the
有关放置在哪里的一些信息
files naturally right this is gonna be
文件自然会是这样
ultimately it's gonna be a running Java
最终它将成为一个正在运行的Java
process running somewhere and so we can
过程在某个地方运行，所以我们可以
provide parameters they get passed to
提供传递给他们的参数
that running process and the same way we
运行过程和我们相同的方式
would any other Springwood application
任何其他Springwood应用程序
as Dashti arguments as environment
作为环境的达什提论点
variables as whenever in this case it's
就像在这种情况下
more convenient to provide them as part
更方便地将它们作为一部分提供
of the definition here so FTP dot
这里的定义，所以FTP点
factory dot host equals localhost right
工厂点主机等于localhost对
we can copy and paste some of these
我们可以复制并粘贴其中一些
values to go a little faster so FTP to
值走得更快一点，所以FTP到
password equals spring FTP type username
密码等于spring FTP类型的用户名
equals J long FTP dot port equals 2121
等于J长FTP点端口等于2121
and so on we can we can do this
等等，我们可以做到这一点
certainly and the the visual tools aware
当然和视觉工具意识到
of them but we can also edit these
他们，但我们也可以编辑这些
properties visually right so we can
视觉上正确的属性，所以我们可以
click on the little gear icon there and
单击那里的小齿轮图标，然后
we can specify for example that we want
我们可以指定例如我们想要的
whatever files appear in the and the
和中出现的所有文件
directory that we're going to monitor to
我们要监视的目录
be split up and published as separate
拆分并单独发布
messages for each line that's called a
每行的消息称为
lines mode we can specify that we want
行模式，我们可以指定我们想要
to monitor the directory called in on my
监视在我的计算机上调用的目录
desktop here and then we're on a monitor
桌面，然后我们在监视器上
only files of type dot txt and then want
只有点txt类型的文件，然后
to prevent duplicates so I think
防止重复，所以我认为
everything else looks fine we also want
其他一切看起来都很好，我们也想要
to specify information about the FTP
指定有关FTP的信息
server itself so I want to automatically
服务器本身，所以我想自动
create the directory and they have to be
创建目录，它们必须是
server if it doesn't exist I want to use
服务器（如果不存在）我要使用
a temporary file name absolutely and I
绝对是一个临时文件名，我
want to use an expression to arrive at
想要使用表达式到达
the name itself so I'll say T math dot
名字本身，所以我会说T数学点
random headers dot found them so what's
随机标头点找到了它们，这是什么
gonna happen is it's going to take the
将会发生的是它将采取
incoming messages which are going to be
即将收到的传入消息
provided by or produced from our file
由我们的文件提供或产生
source and and the spring integration
源与 Spring Integration
for inbound file adapter and it's going
对于入站文件适配器，它会
to contain headers in particular a
包含标题，特别是
header called filename and it normally
标头称为文件名，通常
would use that filename to write the the
将使用该文件名来写
file to the FTP server so if I put a
文件到FTP服务器，所以如果我把
file called food at txt and the in
txt和in中名为food的文件
directory it would get upload
它会上传的目录
to the FTP server as in dot txt but in
到FTP服务器，如点txt，但在
this case I'm gonna divide that in dot
这样的话我要把它分成点
txt by line so I need to make sure that
按行txt，因此我需要确保
even if the even if multiple messages
即使多封邮件
come in with the same file name that
带有相同的文件名
that we differentiate them right we
我们将他们与众不同
don't want them to all override each
不想让他们都覆盖每个
other
其他
so we're gonna use an expression a
所以我们要使用一个表达式
spring expression language expression to
Spring Expression Language 表达
provide a random number and then the
提供一个随机数，然后
name of the file that we originally had
我们最初拥有的文件的名称
okay there we are
好吧，我们在那里
now you can see that the the UI here is
现在您可以看到此处的用户界面是
having a little bit of trouble with a
有点麻烦
spring expression language statement no
Spring Expression Language 声明
problem we just in quote it and
问题，我们只是引用它，
everything seems to sort itself out now
现在一切似乎都在整理
this is certainly interesting enough but
这当然很有趣，但是
this is you know this is all we managed
这是你知道的，这就是我们所管理的
to do last time let's let's go for a
上次要做的，让我们一起去
little bit more interesting solution so
更有趣的解决方案，所以
in what if we could take the lines are
如果我们能接受的话
going to be produced from the file
将要从文件中产生
source and then automatically capitalize
来源，然后自动大写
them using a processor a transformer in
他们使用处理器，变压器
particular so let's go ahead and sort
特别的，让我们继续进行排序
that into the flow by disconnecting this
通过断开连接到流中
this component to that and then connect
将此组件连接到该组件，然后连接
it instead to this and to that so now if
它代替这个和那个，所以现在如果
we look at file mode is lines the
我们来看文件模式是行
directories are the same text up text is
目录是相同的文本向上的文本是
the same everything is basically the
相同的东西基本上是
same but we have to provide a
一样，但我们必须提供
transformer and what this is expecting
变压器，这是什么期望
is a spring spring expression language
是spring春天的表达语言
statements that will say payload to
声明将向
upper case for example hit OK and our
例如大写，点击确定，我们
FTP component is going to work the same
FTP组件将正常工作
as well so everything is as we expect I
一切都如我们所愿
can also imagine wanting to log the data
也可以想像要记录数据
that comes out of this transformer or
从这个变压器出来的
indeed the file source so in this case
确实是文件源，所以在这种情况下
we can use thing called a tap tap is a
我们可以使用一种叫做水龙头的东西
way of taking the data from a message
从消息中获取数据的方式
producing component that is to say a a
生产成分，即aa
source or a processor but not a sink and
源或处理器，但不接收器和
then then diverting it to some other
然后将其转移到其他
component for example a logging sink so
组件，例如一个日志接收器
we can do that by grabbing the tap port
我们可以通过抓住水龙头端口来做到这一点
here and connecting it to the log like
在这里并将其连接到日志
that ok so there we are
好的，所以我们在那里
there's our slightly more sophisticated
还有我们稍微复杂一点的
definition you can see that spring
你可以看到春天的定义
data phone spring cloud and spring flow
数据电话弹簧云和弹簧流量
have given our stream definitions names
给了我们的流定义名称
for us and it's used that name to
对我们来说，这个名字用来
describe the tap here so we're saying
在这里描述水龙头，所以我们说
from the component called transform
来自称为转换的组件
in-stream called stream one divert the
流内称为流一的流
information to the log component right
日志组件右侧的信息
the log component and again we can do
日志组件，我们可以再次做
you can specify the levels for example
您可以指定级别，例如
we can specify some sort of expression
我们可以指定某种表达式
to transform the data whatever one right
正确转换数据
alright so there we are there's our
好吧，所以我们在那里
simple definition let's go ahead and
简单的定义，让我们继续前进，
create that stream or those streams even
创建该流或什至那些流
and we're gonna call this files to FTP
我们将把这个文件称为FTP
and we're gonna call this line to log
我们将呼叫此行进行记录
and when we deploy when we create the
当我们创建
definitions we may as well on the same
我们也可能在同一定义上
swoop and the same sort of go also
俯冲而去
deploy them so let's get create it's
部署它们，让我们开始创建它
gonna go ahead and create our streams
要去创造我们的流
for us
为了我们
we can confirm as much by going to the
我们可以通过转到
streams page and we can see here that
流页面，我们可以在这里看到
there are two things that are deploying
有两件事正在部署
there's States should transition to
有些国家应该过渡到
deployed anytime now right now
现在随时可以部署
deployment just means starting a Java
部署只是意味着启动Java
process using a jar on our local machine
在本地计算机上使用jar进行处理
so we have got two streams which are in
所以我们有两个流
turn composed of several different
转由几个不同的组成
components so even though we've got two
因此即使我们有两个
streams here this may turn into five or
在这里流可能变成五个或
six or four or five or whatever
六个或四个或五个或任何其他
different Java processes I've I guess
我猜是不同的Java进程
I'd have to parse that to figure it out
我必须解析以找出答案
so they're both deployed we can see
所以他们都已经部署了，我们可以看到
exactly how many have been deployed by
到底有多少人被部署
going to the runtime and you haven't it
去运行时，你还没有
you know if we did PSA UX we would see
你知道我们是否做过PSA UX
four processes for Java processes that
Java流程的四个流程
we don't recognize that that's why the
我们不知道这就是为什么
that would be these four processes these
这就是这四个过程
four things if we click on these we can
四件事，如果我们点击这些，我们可以
see that this component is running it
看到该组件正在运行
has a standard error log and a standard
有一个标准的错误日志和一个标准
out log and we can see the URL to Vale
退出日志，我们可以看到淡水河谷的URL
bot and the working directory in which
bot和其中的工作目录
it's running and the standard error and
它正在运行，标准错误和
standard out are particularly useful for
标准输出对于
the log component because after all it's
日志组件，因为毕竟
going to log the data that we see so
将记录我们看到的数据
let's grab that URL there it closed and
让我们在那里获取该URL，然后关闭
let's set the stage okay so we've got an
让我们设置好舞台，以便我们
FTP server running on the local machine
在本地计算机上运行的FTP服务器
in the background we've got a desktop
在后台，我们有一个桌面
here and
在这里和
put directory nothing there let's
放目录什么都没有，让我们
monitor the logs for this component here
在此处监视此组件的日志
so it's up and running you can see the
这样就可以运行了
log sync rabbit application is up and
日志同步Rabbit应用程序已启动并且
running for us and what we're gonna do
为我们而奔跑，我们将要做什么
is we're going to write some data in a
是我们要在其中写入一些数据
text file and then write that text file
文本文件，然后写入该文本文件
to the input directory so I'll just
到输入目录，所以我将
write some names in lowercase so we'll
用小写字母写一些名字
say Mark and Josh and Mark and de and
说马克和乔希，马克和德和
Michael Michael and Illya and Eric and
迈克尔·迈克尔（Michael Michael）和伊莉亚（Illya）以及埃里克（Eric）和
so on save the names here to the input
如此将名称保存到输入
directory names dot txt these are all
目录名称点txt这些都是
lowercase save it there too in we've got
小写字母也保存在那里
nothing in the ws directory or the word
ws目录中没有任何内容或单词
at the FTP WS directory so as soon as we
在FTP WS目录下，
save this we should be able to go to the
保存这一点，我们应该能够去
FTP directory and confirm that
FTP目录并确认
everything has been written in uppercase
一切都写成大写
o desktop FTP WS now there's all the
o桌面FTP WS现在拥有所有功能
files but they don't have any new lines
文件，但没有任何新行
so let's go to the desktop FTP WS
因此，让我们转到桌面FTP WS
directory and find each one ending in
目录并找到每个结尾为
txt we'll loop over each one tap them
txt，我们将遍历每一个点击它们
and then echo a new line and then be
然后回显新行，然后被
done with it so there we are there's all
完成它，所以我们就在那里
the names but now they're uppercase so
名称，但现在它们是大写的，所以
this is one way by which we can create
这是我们创造的一种方式
complex flows is to use that visual
复杂的流程是使用视觉
design time tool that's very very useful
设计时间工具非常有用
because you can interrogate the the
因为您可以讯问
state of the applications you can you
您可以使用的应用程序状态
can manage them so on the same is true
可以管理他们，所以同样如此
for tasks really you just registered a
对于任务，您实际上只是注册了一个
spring batch job in a jar just like you
像你一样在罐子里做Spring Batch处理工作
would our components here you can
我们的组件可以在这里吗
register an application and it could be
注册一个应用程序，它可能是
of type tasks as we can see here right
我们可以在此处看到的类型任务
or anything that can implement
或任何可以实施的
application runner or command line
应用程序运行程序或命令行
weather though that's also a task this
天气虽然这也是一个任务
is one way to interrogate and work with
是一种讯问和合作的方式
the server another is to use the
服务器的另一个是使用
dataflow shell so I thus far been
数据流外壳程序，所以到目前为止
creating things using that visual design
使用视觉设计创造事物
tool because I think that's a very nice
工具，因为我认为这非常好
way to work but there's also a data flow
工作方式，但也有数据流
show that you can download for example
显示您可以下载的示例
on on maven repo com
在Maven Repo com上
or search that maven that org it is here
或搜索该组织的专家
the latest version is one data one
最新版本是一个数据一个
release as of this date but you know
截至该日期发布，但您知道
check back whenever you want I happen to
随时回来找我
have the jar here so I can say John -
这里有罐子，所以我可以说约翰-
jar shell that jar there we are I'm it's
罐子壳，罐子在那里，我是
gonna connect by default to 93 91 93 93
将默认连接到93 91 93 93
which is where the server is running but
服务器正在运行，但是
you can specify where it should find
您可以指定应该在哪里找到
everything if I do app list I can see
我可以看到的所有应用列表
all of the components that are
所有的组件
registered here out of the box ready to
开箱即用在这里注册
use I can see the streams write the same
使用我可以看到流写相同
information all that same information
所有相同的信息
that we used and interrogated and worked
我们使用，审讯和工作的
with in the in the data flow sort of
在数据流中
server itself is available from the
服务器本身可从
shell and anybody can point their shell
外壳，任何人都可以指出他们的外壳
to an instance of the server even if you
到服务器的实例，即使您
don't have access to the server itself
没有访问服务器本身的权限
directly all right with this we've
直接就可以了
looked ever so briefly and how to create
看起来如此简短以及如何创建
really interesting sort of complex
真的很有趣
solutions we've looked at how you can
我们研究过的解决方案
build upon what we learned in our videos
建立在我们从视频中学到的知识的基础上
looking at spring cloud dataflow and
看着春天的云数据流和
spring cloud stream and spring
春天的云流和春天
integration to build really really sort
整合真的很不错
of complex stream processing solutions
复杂的流处理解决方案
for potentially endless amount of data
潜在的无穷数据量
or batch or task eccentric kinds of
或批处理或任务怪异的
workloads because spring cloud dataflow
工作量，因为春季云数据流
manages the state we have an easy way to
管理状态，我们有一个简单的方法
monitor and administer these jobs these
监视和管理这些工作
tasks we can launch tasks I mean
我们可以启动任务的任务
launched jobs in an easy to wear easy to
穿着容易穿上衣服
understand way and it's very easy to see
了解方式，很容易看到
it's very easy to see how we could build
很容易看到我们如何建立
more complex solutions by composing
通过组成更复杂的解决方案
these little Lego bricks right this is
这些小乐高积木对，这是
not even code what I've done here is
甚至没有编码我在这里所做的
really I mean you could you could build
真的，我的意思是你可以建立
complex solutions for anything one use
适用于任何用途的复杂解决方案
case and I quite like is remediation
案子，我很喜欢补救
right imagine building a flow that
想象一下建立一个流程
looked at the logs coming off of Cloud
查看了来自Cloud的日志
Foundry for example you can you can
例如铸造厂就可以
register the Cloud Foundry laga Gator
注册Cloud Foundry laga Gator
source and then you can write a
源，然后您可以编写一个
processor that keeps only the data that
仅保留数据的处理器
matches a certain format and then write
匹配某种格式然后写
a you know take that data and then write
一个你知道的数据，然后写
it out to a sink in this case a field
在这种情况下，它会流到水槽
value counter so you can actually keep a
价值计数器，因此您实际上可以保留
counter in Redis for every occurrence of
Redis中的计数器，每次出现
a message coming through that processor
通过该处理器的消息
that that basically does grep so now you
那基本上可以做grep，所以现在你
have an easy way to
有一个简单的方法
you know based on that counter and
你知道基于那个计数器
another flow you could say okay if that
另一个流程，你可以说好吗
counter becomes greater than ten then
然后计数器变得大于十
maybe we should send an email or
也许我们应该发送电子邮件或
somebody should we start a server or or
有人应该我们启动服务器或
something right and that's it's easy to
正确的事情很容易
pull that stuff together very
把这些东西拉在一起
declaratively right and you can describe
声明上正确，您可以描述
ad-hoc flows so even if you haven't
临时流动，即使您没有
thought of every possible integration
想到所有可能的整合
flow you can sort of rework and create
流程，您可以进行一些返工和创建
new ones on the fly alright thank you
新的飞行中，好的，谢谢
very much see you in the next video
非常期待在下一个视频中见到您
you
您